Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance is hiring for
Digital Insurance Advisor role| Apply Now.
JOB ROLE: Digital Life Insurance Advisor.
Location - PARTTIME,WORK FROM HOME,PAN INDIA.
JOB DESCRIPTION:
For information on job role, please submit
your details and our representative will connect
with you to explain you in detail about the same.
Complete your Documentation. Following is the
list of documents required for applying to the
IRDAI government exam.
Aadhar card, Pan card,
Highest qualification marksheet(minimum
12ᵗʰ pass), Digital Signature photo,
Cancelled cheque, Passport size photo,
Nominee date of birth and Name.
Get trained for the IRDAI exam.
We provide you training to help
you prepare for the IRDAI exam. Also, we
help you with special support & additional
training on products, marketing models & other
aspects related to life insurance industry.
Pass the examination & get your business code.
Once you successfully clear the exam you
will be given IRDAI license,
visiting cards & certificate.
Start providing solutions to
people & earn amazing payouts.
Earn exciting prizes, incentives and rewards
after providing solutions to your clients.
The representative will call you back once you
submit your details to help you check eligibility.
However, the minimum eligibility criteria is
you should be aged more than 25 years and passed
class 12ᵗʰ examination.
Education Required:
Applicant can be a businessman, distributor
of financial products, housewife, etc.
The representative will call you back once
you submit your details to help you check
eligibility. However, the minimum eligibility
criteria is you should be aged more than 25
years and passed class 12ᵗʰ examination.
He or she should have passed 10th Standard
or equivalent examination from
a recognized board/institution
Skills Required:
You must have Excellent spoken Telugu Language.
You must have proficiency
Proficient with MS-Office.
SALARY:35K EXPECTED.
link provided in
description. don't forget like, share and
subscribe to our channel for more updates.